hardreset99.com 2017-01-11

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Privacy Policy in order for you to understand how we collect data and how we will use that data for future purpose. The following outlines our privacy policy. 

  * Before collecting personal information, we will seriously identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use of personal information (Data) solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us (HardReset99.com Team) and for other compatible purposes.
  * Personal data or information should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate (more than 95%), complete, and up to date.
  * We will only retain personal information or data as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will make readily available to customers or visitor or user information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal data.
  * We will collect personal data by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * We will protect personal data by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, copying, disclosure, use or modification.

We are committed to conducting our online business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information or data is protected and maintained.

**Third-party disclosure :**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable data or Information.

**Third-party links :**

We do not include or offer any third-party products or services on our website.
